export const javaIntermediateQuestions = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: "Which keyword is used to inherit a class?",
        options: ["implements", "extends", "inherits", "super"],
        answer: "extends"
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: "What is the default value of an object reference?",
        options: ["0", "null", "undefined", "false"],
        answer: "null"
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: "Which collection allows duplicate elements?",
        options: ["Set", "List", "Map", "None"],
        answer: "List"
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: "What is used to handle exceptions?",
        options: ["try-catch", "if-else", "do-while", "switch"],
        answer: "try-catch"
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: "Which keyword prevents method overriding?",
        options: ["static", "final", "const", "abstract"],
        answer: "final"
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: "ArrayList is part of which package?",
        options: ["java.lang", "java.util", "java.io", "java.net"],
        answer: "java.util"
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: "Which access modifier gives most restricted access?",
        options: ["public", "protected", "default", "private"],
        answer: "private"
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: "Method overloading is:",
        options: ["Same name, diff params", "Same name, same params", "Diff name, same params", "None"],
        answer: "Same name, diff params"
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: "Which keyword is used to define an interface?",
        options: ["interface", "class", "abstract", "implements"],
        answer: "interface"
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: "Can an abstract class be instantiated?",
        options: ["Yes", "No", "Sometimes", "Only main"],
        answer: "No"
    }
];
